<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Vegan City final</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="logo_heading">My Vegan City</string>
    <string name="search_city_body">You can use this app to search your city for vegan brands in your local grocery stores and find vegan restaurants.</string>
    <string name="vegan101_body">So you may be asking yourself - what does "vegan" mean? Vegan simply means food that doesn\'t have any animal-based ingredients and is 100% made from plant sources. The good news is most food, excluding dairy and meat, is 75% or more made up of plants anyway. Also, ANYTHING you eat now has a vegan version. \n \n
        Eating vegan means you should be adding a huge assortment of foods to your diet, instead of just taking a few away. Vegan food is also always healthier for one reason - it\'s cholesterol free since only animal ingredients contain it. So if the nutrition label shows the food has cholesterol, then it\'s not vegan. \n \n
        Animal ingredients include honey, gelatin, milk (and derivatives such as casein), meat, and animal fats and excretions and sometimes use names that can be confusing and you may not be sure what the ingredient is. An example of this is shellac, which comes from bugs. One other thing to watch out for is natural flavors and mono- and diglycerides because sometimes these can come from animals. \n \n
        It\'s best to do a web search on any ingredients that are not obvious.  If after doing a web search you determine that the ingredient can be either plant or animal-based, then you can try doing a search for the product and the word \"vegan\" and see if any reliable sources, such as the manufacturer\'s website or a nationally known vegan website, can confirm if the product is vegan or not. \n \n
        We know this sounds like a lot of work but the good news is sometimes researching ingredients on the package isn\'t necessary because the package will say \"vegan\" on it. This is becoming more common as veganism grows. However, if the package has a \"V\" on it, make sure the \"V\" stands for vegan and not vegetarian or if it says \"plant-based\" the product may still not be completely vegan because some plant-based products contain honey or milk. You can also look for the certified vegan seals from Vegan.org and The Vegan Society, and the certified plant based seal from the Plant Based Foods Association. All of these seals indicate the food is vegan. \n \n
        You probably already know that fruits and veggies are vegan for the most part but did you know that a lot of other food you already eat is vegan too. Here\'s a list of common food you probably already eat: Captain Crunch cereal, most flavors of Oreos, Nutter Butter cookies, Pillsbury crescent rolls, Wheat Thins crackers, Kellog\'s Club crackers, unfrosted strawberry Pop-Tarts, Ritz crackers, Bisquick mix, La Croix sparkling water, Hershey\'s syrup, Life cereal, Red Bull drinks, Sour Patch Kids, Lays regular and BBQ chips, Thomas\' plain, everything and blueberry bagels, Cracker Jacks, Airheads candy, Fritos, Fruit by the Foot, Ruffles original chips, Ore-Ida Tater Tots, Pringles Original Chips, Jell-O cook and serve vanilla pudding (use plant milk), Swedish Fish candy, original Twizzlers candy, SuperPretzel original soft pretzel, monster energy drinks, original SunChips, Kool-Aid, Dots candy, unfrosted mini wheats cereal, original triscuit crackers, blueberry BelVita breakfast biscuits, Chocolate Teddy Grahams, Skittles, and so much more.
    </string>
</resources>